Guide to the Menu collection, 1851-[ca.1990].
Menu collection,
- Assorted US Menus
  - Hotel St. Regis, 1907-01-31 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel St. Regis, 1906-11-03 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel St. Regis, 1906-06-28 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel St. Regis, 1906-06-28 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel St. Regis, 1906-11-25 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Hotel St. Regis, 1906-10-19 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - House of Ming, Undated (Box 62, Folder 9)
    Strougsburg, PA
  - House of Ming, 1971-08-03 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - The House of Murphy, Undated (Box 59, Folder 7)
    Los Angeles
  - Howard Johnson, 1973-04-14 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    Worcester, MA
  - Hudson's Seafood, 1990-03 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    Front page titled "Dock Talk," but it is a menu for Hudson's Seafood. Originally the document was mislabled.
    Hitlon Head Island, SC
  - Hunan, Undated (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Huval's Authentic Cajun Restaurant, Undated (Box 60, Folder 8)
    Salem, MA
  - The Inner circle Presents "All Vulnerable" at the Hotel Astor, 1933-02-18 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - International Geneva Association 1929 New York Branch's 25th Anniversary, 1929-10-14 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - International Geneva Association 1954 New York Branch Golden Jubilee Supper Dance, 1954-01-18 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Invitation to reception in honor of Her Imperial Highness, Princess Ashraf Pahlavi in the Statler Ballroom, Undated (Box 59, Folder 8)
    The dating of this event is unclear. It took place on a Thursday, the thirteenth of November under president Dale R. Corson. So, this means that the event either took place November 13, 1975, or Thursday, November 13, 1969.
  - J.B. Winberie, 1986-03-15 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    Princeton, NJ
  - Johnny Harris, 1936 Souvenir Menu, 1936-01-01-1936-12-31 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    Savannah, GA
  - JT's Place, 1982-10-09 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    Ardmore, PA
  - Juleps, 1992-02-13 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    Hilton Head Island, SC
  - Justin's, 1984-12-07 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Kansas City Associated General Contractors Dinner Menu, Undated (Box 57, Folder 8)
    Kansas City, MI
  - Kansas City Associated General Contractors Dinner Menu, Undated (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Keepers II, Undated (Box 60, Folder 10)
    Marlboro, MA
  - Kens Pub, Undated (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - The Keys, Undated (Box 57, Folder 8)
    Indianapolis, IN
  - Keys Fisheries Market and Marina, 2003-03-14 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    Florida Keys, FL
  - Kings Dinner Menu, Undated (Box 57, Folder 8)
    Illinois, USA
  - Kyoto, Undated (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Lahaina Broiler, 1974-06-04 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    Maui, HI
  - Landfall, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    Cape Cod, Ma
  - Legal Sea Foods, Undated (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Lillian's, 1987-07-01-1987-07-31 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    This menus is from Saratoga Springs, but Lillian's has another location in Albany.
    Saratoga Springs, NY
  - Liz-Jon Cajun Cuisine, Undated (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - The Lobster, 1946-11-19 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Lobster House, 1981-07-30 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    Avalon, NJ
  - Lobster House, 1976-08 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - The Lobster House, Undated (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - The Lobster House, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Locke-Ober Café, Undated (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Locke-Ober Café, Undated (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Locke-Ober Café, a brief history and abridged menu, Undated (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Longfellow's Wayside Inn, 1979-10-08 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    Sudbury, MA
  - Louis Pappas, 1978-06-07 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    Tampa, FL
  - Lox, Stock & Bagel: The Uncommon Deli, Dessert Menu, Undated (Box 60, Folder 11)
    No geographical information on the menu.
  - Love's Take Out, Undated (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Luchow's Restaurant, 1963-03-05 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Luncheon in Honor of the representatives: The United Nations, 1946-10-23 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Le Madrigal, Undated (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Maestro Luncheon, Undated (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Mammy's Shanty, Undated (Box 57, Folder 10)
    Atlanta, GA
  - Mandalay Burmese Restaurant, Undated (Box 60, Folder 12)
    Claims to be the first Burmese Restaurant in the US.
  - The Manor, 2013-12-01-2013-12-31 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Mariner Inn, Undated (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Mario's Restaurant, Undated (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Marra's, 2000-08-15 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    Roseland, NJ
  - Martell's, Undated (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Maud Chez Elle, 1970-10-30 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Maxwell's Plum, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Mcdonald's, Breakfast Menu, Undated (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - The Meeting Place, 1980-03-26 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    Madison, NJ
  - Menu, 1906-04-20 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Mexican Rose, 1985-10-11 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Mitzi Holmes Lager House, Undated (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Moishe's Gourmet Delicatessen, Undated (Box 60, Folder 12)
    Berkley, CA
  - Le Moal, 1972-09-27 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Monk's Court, 1973-04-28 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Monte Proser's Copacabana, Undated (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Moshulu, 1984-02-18 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Mothers, 1980-04-30 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Mr. B's, Undated (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Nashville Menus, Undated (Box 59, Folder 13)
    Nashville, TN
  - The Navarre, Historical Pamphlet, Undated (Box 57, Folder 11)
    Denver, CO
  - The Navarre, Historical Pamphlet, Undated (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - The Navarre, Dinner Menu, Undated (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - The Navarre, Dinner Menu, Undated (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - The Navarre, Dinner Menu, Undated (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - The New Orleans Café, 1985-02-09 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    A collection of menus from Nashville that someone has compiled and published. Additionally, a few extra restaurant recommendations have been hand-written in the back.
  - New York State Hotel Association, 1929-11-15 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - New York Racing Association, 1954-09-24 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - New York Times Articles on Menu Collecting and Luchow's closing, 1982-03-24 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - The New Yorker, "They Know me Here," July 23, 1984, 1984-07-23 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - The Newporter, Undated (Box 56, Folder 13)
    Newport Beach, California
  - Nico's Pier 17, 1977-09-09 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    Paramus, NJ
  - Niederstein's, 1989-11-01 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Nirvana, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - The NM Café, Undated (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Non-Menu Materials, Undated (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Non-Menu Materials, Undated (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - El Nuevo Salon Imperial, 1933-09-29 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Official Dinner of the Hotel Association of New York City inc. to Visiting Latin-American Hotelmen members of the Inter-American Hotel Association, Undated (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Old Heidelberg, Undated (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - The Old Mill, 1988-11-23 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    Westminster, MA
  - The Old Salmon Inn, Undated (Box 60, Folder 14)
    Corinth, NY
  - The Old Stone Mill, 1985-04-17 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    Skaneateles, NY
  - The Olde Bryan Inn, 1987-07-01-1987-07-31 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - O'neil's Bar and Restaurant, Undated (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - On the Waterfront, 1988-11-29 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    Jersey City, NJ
  - Orangerie, Dinner Menu, 1939-03-15 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Orangerie, Dinner Menu, 1939-03-17 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Orangerie, Lunch Menu, 1939-03-18 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Orangerie, Lunch Menu, 1939-03-20 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Orangerie, Lunch Menu, 1939-03-15 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Orangerie, Lunch Menu, 1939-03-13 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Orangerie, Lunch Menu, 1939-03-14 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Orangerie, Lunch Menu, 1939-03-15 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Orso, 1993-11-17 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Oyster Bar & Restaurant, 1988-03-01 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Pacific Northwest Potlatch Welcoming the Delegates the Associated General Contractors of America Presented by the Seattle Chapter and the Mountain Pacific Chapter- Mid-yeark Board Meeting, 1957-09-08 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    Seattle, WA
  - The Paddock, Undated (Box 60, Folder 15)
    Hyannis Port, MA
  - Pagliacci, Undated (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Pals Cabin, 1974-01-26 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Pals Cabin, 1974-01-26 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Pan American World Airways Beverages and Diversions, 1955-11-02 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Paoletti's, 1973-03-01 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    Miami Beach, FL
  - Paul's Fish & Chips, Undated (Box 60, Folder 15)
    Wakefield, MA
  - Le Pavillon, Undated (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Le Pavillon, Undated (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Le Pavillon, Undated (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - The Peacock Inn, 1980-10-11 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Pearl's, 1978-02-15 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Pedro Diego's, Undated (Box 60, Folder 15)
    Haverhill, MA
  - Peking Garden, Chinese Pastry Menu, Undated (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Peking Garden, Take out Menu, Undated (Box 60, Folder 15)
    Menu contains business card, postcard, and three fortunes from fortune cookies.
  - Penthouse, 1973-12-22 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    Great Gorge
  - Perditas of Charleston (Box 56, Folder 15)
    Charleston, SC
  - Petite Marmite, Undated (Box 61, Folder 11)
    Palm Beach, FL
  - Pierre au Tunnel, 1994-02-16 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Pierre au Tunnel, 1986-03-19 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Pineapple Hill, 1974-06-05 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    Lahaina Maui, HI
  - Pipers, 1980-01-04 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    Florida
  - Piraeus MY Love, 1970-01-29 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    Includes a note with some Greek translation, a note about the meal, a wine label, as well as a catalogue for a January 13-31, 1970 Paul Camacho Exhibit at William Zeirler Inc.
  - Planet Hollywood, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Poor Henry's Saloon, 1976-10-10 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    Montville, NJ
  - Port O' Georgetown, 1971-10-08 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - The President: Blue Ribbon Transatlantic Flight, Pan America Menu, 1955-11-21 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Primavera Restaurant, Undated (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - The Prime Time, 1988-03-16 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    Fairfield, NJ
  - Promenade Café, 1948-07-07 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Promenade Café, 1950-10-08 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - The Proud Popover, Undated (Box 60, Folder 15)
    Location based on information found on the FB fanpage for the now closed restaurant.
  - The Prow and Pub, 1947-04-17 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Publick House, 1983-10-30 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    Chester, NJ
  - Putnam & Thurston's, 1973-04-14 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Les Pyrenees, 1988-02-20 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Les Pyrenees, 1977-07-12 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Quail Hill Inn, 1972-09-29 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Quarterdeck Seafoods, Undated (Box 60, Folder 16)
    Maynard, MA
  - El Rancho Hotel Mermaid Room Dinner Menu, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    Millbrae, CA
  - Really Special Home Made Foods, Undated (Box 61, Folder 13)
    Stockbridge, MA
  - The Red Lion Inn, Breakfast Menu, Undated (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - The Red Lion Inn, Dinner Menu, Undated (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - The Red Lion Inn, Wine Menu, Undated (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Rene Pujol, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Rene Pujol, 1989-11-15 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Restaurant Broussard, Undated (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Restaurant Business Cards, Undated (Box 60, Folder 17)
    A variety of business cards from restaurants all stapled to a board. Various locations.
  - Restaurant-Café Kainz, Undated (Box 62, Folder 17)
    Hohenschwangau, Germany
  - Restaurante del Paseo, Undated (Box 59, Folder 16)
    Santa Barbara, CA
  - Restaurante del Paseo, Undated (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Reuben's, 1963-.03-07 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - The Ritz Carlton, Cornell Society of Hotelmen Christmas Dinner, 1978-12-12 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - The Ritz Carlton, Cornell Society of Hotelmen Dinner, 1977-12-12 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Le Rivage, 1989-01-19 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Roast Beef and Brew, 1971-01-13 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Rocco's, Undated (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Rocktide, 1992-07-26 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    Boothbay Harbor, ME
  - Rod's 1890's Ranch House, 1986-01-10 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    Convent Station, NJ
  - The Romagnoli's Table, Undated (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Romanoffs, 1951-07-03 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    USA
  - Room Service Menu, Undated (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Royal Orleans, 1987-05-09 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    No geographical information available on the menu save that the Royal Orleans is not in New Orleans. It may have originally been in Orlando, although this is unclear.
  - Russian Tea Room, Undated (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Russian Tea Room, 1972-12-08 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Saddlerock Grill, Undated (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - The Sagmore, 1987-07-15 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    Bolton Landing, NY
  - Saltwater Café, 1994-03-04 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Samoset Resort, 1992-07-24 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    Rockport, ME
  - Sardi's, 1990-11-14 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Sardi's, 1973-04-04 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Saugus International Airport, Undated (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Saugus International Airport, Weekend Specials, Undated (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Saugus International Airport, Review, "Joy of Eating", 1981-04-02 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Savoy Grill, 1955-11-30 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Sayat Nova, 1964 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Scala del Nonna, Undated (Box 62, Folder 18)
    Montclair, NJ
  - Schroeder's Restaurant, Undated (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Sheraton Hotel, 1974-06-01 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Simplon, Undated (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Skywalk Café, Hotel Astor, 1938-07-14 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Stock Yard Inn, Undated (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Stock Yard Inn, Undated (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - The Society of the Friendly Sons of St. Patrick in the City of New York, 1938-03-17 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - The Society of the Friendly Sons of St. Patrick in the City of New York, 1931-03-17 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Somerset House, Undated (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Somerset House, Undated (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - The Sportsman Sentinel, 1971-01-01-1971-12-31 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    Blackslee, PA
  - Spring Street Natural Restaurant, Undated (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - S.S. Nieuw Amsterdam, 1927-02-02 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - St. Louis Crepe Shoppe and Restaurant, Undated (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Stadium Club, 1980-09-04 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Stage Deli of New York, Undated (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Statler Inn Main Dining Room Guest Chef's Dinner, 1972-11-20 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    The guest ghef was Mr. Sector or Mr. Secter, the menu does not spell his name the same way throughout.
  - Camp Susan Curtis Benefit Dinner Menu, 1977-10-03 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Swiss Center Restaurants, 1974-05-08 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Talia's Delicatessen and Fine Continental Restaurant, Undated (Box 60, Folder 19)
    Manhattan Beach, CA
  - Tavern on the Green, 1988-11-16 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Tavern on the Green, 1978-02-19 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Tavern on the Green, 1972-09-01 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - The Tennis Club, 1948-10-01-1948-10-01 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    Palm Springs, CA
  - Testimonial Luncheon Tendered Captain Hermann Kohl, Baron E.G.v.Hunefeld, and Major James C. Fitzmaurice in Honor of their Historic Flight from Europe to America in the Junker Plane "Bremen", 1928-05-07 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - The Thomas Hunter Association of Grammar School No. 35, 1920-11-20 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Tomaiolo's White Cliffs, 1975-11-01 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    Northboro, MA
  - Top O' the Mast, 1989-07-12 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    Seaside Park, NJ
  - Top O' the Mast, 1979-08-15 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Top of the Fair, 1964-01-01-1965-12-31 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - El Torito, Undated (Box 60, Folder 19)
    Encino, California
  - Town Tavern, 1973-06-12 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Town Tavern, 1980-06-27 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Trader Vic's, 1974-06-08 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    Waikiki, HI
  - Truffles, Undated (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - The Tulip Tree, 1984-11-13 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    Westchester, NY
  - Il Tulipano, 1996-02-14 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    Cedar Grove, NJ
  - Il Tulipano, 1988-06-02 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Twenty-Fifth Wedding Anniversary of Mr. and Mrs. Samuel Cowen, 1928-06-28 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - United States-Azerbaijan Chamber of Commerce Presidential Banquet to Honor the President of the Republic of Azerbaijan His Excellency Heydar Aliyev, 2001-09-11 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - University Club of Los Angeles, Main Dining Room Luncheon Menu, 1956-05-28 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Uno Pizzeria, Undated (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Untitled, 1986-09-21-1986-12-21 (Box 60, Folder 23)
    Large white menu with no restaurant name or location attached to it.
  - La Valencia Hotel, 1952-08-15 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    La Jolla, CA
  - La Valencia Hotel, 1948-03-01-1948-03-31 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - The Vanderbilt Hotel Menu, Undated (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Le Vert Galant, 1974-04-24 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    Includes a short note on the owner's day.
  - Vonachens Junction, Undated (Box 57, Folder 16)
    Peoria, IL
  - The Victorian Room, Lunch Menu, 1951-05-26 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - The Victorian Room, Dinner Menu, 1951-05-26 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Victoria Station, Dinner Menu, Undated (Box 60, Folder 21)
    Lists various different locations of restaurant.
  - Victoria Station, Lunch Menu, Undated (Box 60, Folder 21)
    Chain restaurant with several locations.
  - The Victorian, Undated (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Viennese Pastries Café, 1993-12-09 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    Bethlehem, PA
  - The Waldorf Dinner Menu, 1893-03-16 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - The Waldorf Lunch Menu, 1893-03-16 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Water Front, 1984-08-16 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Weylus, Undated (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - The Whitebrier, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - William Penn Inn, 2013-11-15 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    Gwynedd, PA
  - The Wine Vaults of Hotel Imperial, Undated (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Winter Palace, 1939-10-28 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - The World of Fine Dining: Manhattan (Box 59, Folder 21)
    Collection of menus from New York.
  - Ye Olde Union Oyster House, Undated (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - La Zaragozana (Box 61, Folder 16)
    San Juan, PR
- Assorted Canadian Menus
  - Restaurant Continental, 1984-08-20 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    Quebec, Canada
  - The Keg, 1984-08-23 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    Toronto, Canada
  - Au "400" Chez Lelarge, Undated (Box 58, Folder 1)
    Montreal, Canada
  - Auberge Du Pommier, Undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Balinese Room, Undated (Box 58, Folder 2)
    Canada
  - Bastogne, Undated (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Bastogne Coffee Shop, Undated (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Bastogne Terrace, Undated (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - The Benvenuto, Undated (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - The Brant Inn, Undated (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Le Cabaret, Undated (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Le Cabaret, Wine List, Undated (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Cafe de la Terrasse, Undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Café Henry Burger, 1960-01-03-1960-01-03 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    Hull, Canada
  - Café Martin, Undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - The Royal Alexander Hote, New Years Menu, 1960-12-31-1961-01-01 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    Winnipeg, Canada
  - Chateau Frontenac, Undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Chateau Frontenac, Afternoon Tea Menu, Undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Chateau Frontenac, Dinner Menu, Undated (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - La Chaumiere, Undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Clans Coffee Shop, Undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
    Burlington, Canada
  - Clans Coffee Shop, Breakfast at, Undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - The Coffee House, Undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Danny's Restaurant, Undated (Box 57, Folder 3)
    Bathurst, New Brunswick
  - Desjardins, Undated (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Dutch Sisters Inn, Undated (Box 58, Folder 4)
    The Inn seems to have been a chain. The menu identifies it as having locations in Toronto and Ontario, but it does not specify further.
    Toronto and Ontario, Canada
  - Estaminet, Undated (Box 58, Folder 5)
    Ontario, Canada
  - Estaminet, Undated (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - The Guild Inn, 1961-01-10-1961-01-10 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    Scarborough, Canada
  - Hale-Kai, Undated (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Hy's Steak House, Undated (Box 58, Folder 7)
    Calgary, Canada
  - Laurentien Coffee Shop, Undated (Box 58, Folder 8)
    Beauport, Quebec
  - Lichee Garden, Undated (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - The Old Mill, Undated (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - The Park Plaza, 1961-01-10-1961-01-10 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - The Park Plaza, Undated (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - The Palliser, Roomservice Menu, Undated (Box 58, Folder 10)
    Calgary Canada
  - The Palliser, Western Style Steak Specials, Undated (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Pierre's, Undated (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Rickman's Luncheon Menus, Undated (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Rickman's Special Holiday Menus, Undated (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Rickman's Noon Menu, Undated (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Ruby Foo's Banquets Menu, Undated (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Ruby Foo's Wine List, Undated (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - RV Princess Mary, 1961-01-10-1961-01-10 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    Includes ephemera.
    Victoria, Canada
  - La Reine Elizabeth, Undated (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Salle Bonaventure, Undated (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Selkirk Room, The Royal Alexandra, Breakfast Menu, Undated (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Selkirk Room, The Royal Alexandra, Dinner Menu, Undated (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Sheraton Hotel, King Edward, The Pickwick Theatre Café Pesents "Up-Tempo 61", Undated (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Sheraton Hotel, King Edward, Golden Grill, Undated (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Sheraton Hotel, King Edward, Oak Roam Luncheon Menu, Undated (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Sheraton Hotel, King Edward, Main Dining Room Luncheon Menu, Undated (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Victoria Room, Undated (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - York Pioneer, Undated (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - York Pioneer, Undated (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - York Pioneer, Undated (Box 57, Folder 17)
- Assorted International Menus
  - A l'Ecu de France, 1977-09-18 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    London, England
  - American Colony Munich Thanksgiving Dinner and Dance-Card, 1908-11-26 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    Munich, Germany
  - Anderson's, Undated (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Mexico City, Mexico
  - Annual Government and Business Dinner, 1996, 1996-10-17 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    Germany
  - Auberge Du Coucou, 1955-05-08 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    Paris, France
  - Ball Dinner, Beacon Hotel, 1905-01-20 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    Crowborough, England
  - Beacon Hotel Brochure, 1905-01-20 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Bistrot du Sommelier, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Le Bistroquet, Undated (Box 56, Folder 2)
    France
  - Brighton and Hove Golf Club Annual Dinner Menu, 1905-12-15 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    Brighton, England
  - Brighton Hotels' Interest Association Dinner Menu, 1906-03-21 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - The Brighton Master Builder's Association Twelfth Annual Dinner at the Hotel Metropole, 1905-03-02 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - The Brighton Master Builder's Association Twelfth Annual Dinner at the Hotel Metropole, 1906-03-06 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Le Bistroquet, Undated (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Boscombe Lodge, no. 2158, Brother Edward Henry Bone, Worshipful Master, Installation Banquet, Undated (Box 56, Folder 2)
    Boscombe, England
  - Cecil, 1931-06-10 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    Oslo, Norway
  - Cecil, Smorbrodliste (sandwich list), 1931-06-10 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - the China Club, Undated (Box 56, Folder 3)
    Beijing, China
  - the China Club, Undated (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Le Coc, 1962-06-01-1962-06-30 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Compton Cricket Club Tenth Annual Dinner and Concert, 1904-10-29 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Concert, Vocal and Instrumental, at the Hotel Metropole, 1905-12-25 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - La Corne d'Or, Advertisement of Special Dinner by Chef Michel Trosgros, 1992-01-13-1992-01-18 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    Istanbul, Turkey
  - La Corne d'Or, Menu of Special Dinner by Chef Michel Trosgros, 1992-01-13-1992-01-18 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    This menu is signed by chef.
  - Cupecoy Beach Resort, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    St. Martin
  - Die Gute Bayerische Kuche, Undated (Box 62, Folder 4)
    Garmish, Germany
  - Doney, Undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
    Florence, Italy